#### Contact

jennifer.giangiulio@gmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/jennifergiangiulio-rn-bsn-ocn-673453a (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Pediatrics

# Jennifer Giangiulio RN, BSN, OCN

Oncology Registered Nurse

Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

# Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with 14 years experience; demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Strong experience and professionally skilled in Nurse Navigation, Medical-Surgical, Oncology, Chemotherapy, and Healthcare.

OCN and BCLS certified.

## Experience

Penn Medicine, University of Pennsylvania Health System Breast Cancer Nurse Navigator February 2016 - June 2019 (3 years 5 months) Greater Philadelphia Area

The Nurse Navigator functions as an advocate, interpreter, educator and counselor for the oncology patient, their family, and referring public. The nurse navigator is responsible for ensuring patients with an oncology diagnosis receive quality and comprehensive coordinated services. The nurse navigator coordinates care throughout the care continuum in collaboration with the multidisciplinary team.

#### Merck

Oncology Clinical Nurse Educator July 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 8 months) NJ/Philadelphia

- -Provided nursing in-services using approved educational materials and used this as an added touch point with customers; Educating nursing staff, physicians and pharmacists.
- -Continued to develop relationships with nurses and staff throughout my territory and help support the sales team.
- -Experience in building customer relationships with key nursing organizations, targeted accounts, ONS, and other identified key customers.

- -Actively participated in the product launch of a new Immunotherapy drug Keytruda.
- -Communicate and follow-up with nursing and office staff on infusions, challenges and patient needs; Ensure the ongoing education of nurses to help them better manage immune related side effects and effectively teach their patients.
- -Help nursing staff achieve better patient outcomes and provide insight on best practices by providing training and follow-up as needed.
- -Territory consisted of NJ, Philadelphia and SE PA.

### Children's Hospital Los Angeles (CHLA)

Travel RN

November 2013 - February 2014 (4 months)

Pediatric Outpatient Infusion Center.

Solid Tumors/ Leukemics/ BMT

Experience in administering Chemotherapy, Bio Therapeutic Agents, Blood Transfusions, IVIG.

Inserting IV's, managing PICC and PAC lines.

Education to patient and patient families.

PALS, APHON certified.

#### St. Judes Medical Center

Travel RN

August 2012 - November 2013 (1 year 4 months)

Fullerton

Inpatient Medical/ Surgical Oncology Unit

Responsible for admissions and discharges of patients.

Coordination of oncology patients and detailed history from patient and family.

Care of patients with palliative care; end of life care and improvement of comfort; PCA's.

Managed drains, colostomies, feeding tubes (feeding pumps, NG tubes, peg tubes, TPN), chest tubes, trachs (suctioning).

Knowledgeable of PPE, Contact Isolation Precautions.

Cedars-Sinai

Travel RN

May 2012 - August 2012 (4 months)

Obtained assessments, history for pre- operative and post operative patients.

Worked side by side with physicians involving mastectomies and thyroidectomies.

Assisted physicians with breast biopsies.

Attended multidisciplinary rounds regarding patient cases.

#### **UCSF Medical Center**

Travel RN

July 2011 - May 2012 (11 months)

Focus on Solid Tumors

Responsible for the coordination of the oncology patients' and history from patient and family.

Interpretation of diagnostic tests with Physician/NP/Pharmacists.

Administration of Chemotherapy, Anti-neoplastic agents, hormone affecting Injections.

Care of patients participating in various clinical trials.

#### Memorial Medical Center

Travel RN

May 2011 - July 2011 (3 months)

Inpatient Medical/ Surgical Oncology Unit

Responsible for admissions and discharges of patients.

Coordination of oncology patients and detailed history from patient and family.

Care of patients with palliative care; end of life care and improvement of comfort; PCA's.

Managed drains, colostomies, feeding tubes (feeding pumps, NG tubes, peg tubes, TPN), chest tubes, trachs (suctioning).

Knowledgeable of PPE, Contact Isolation Precautions.

#### Cedars-Sinai Medical Center

Travel RN

October 2010 - May 2011 (8 months)

Inpatient Medical/ Surgical Oncology Unit

Administration of Chemotherapy/ Biotherapeutic Agents, Blood Transfusion.

Responsible for admissions and discharges of patients.

Coordination of oncology patients and detailed history from patient and family.

Care of patients with palliative care; end of life care and improvement of comfort; PCA's.

Managed drains, colostomies, feeding tubes (feeding pumps, NG tubes, peg tubes, TPN), chest tubes, trachs (suctioning).

Knowledgeable of PPE, Contact Isolation Precautions.

#### New York-Presbyterian Hospital

Clinical Nurse II

September 2006 - August 2010 (4 years)

Inpatient Medical/Surgical- Hematology Oncology Unit

Acquired position as charge nurse after 2 yrs at organization.

Managed RN assignments for shift; admissions and discharges.

Dealt with any mishaps/ problems that may arise with staff, patients/family,

health care staff in collaboration with Nursing office.

Took care of own set of patients on top of other responsibilities.

## Education

College of Mount Saint Vincent

B.S in Nursing, Major: Nursing/ Minor: Biology · (2002 - 2006)